( Pulsating )
( labored breathing )
(thuds)
I have to say
I was impressed.
You had taken a risk.
Getting your hands dirty.
You know, we were
gonna have those biters
for our little
Michonne and--
Milton: You were gonna use them
on whoever showed up.
That's right.
Hey,
Because we didn't
have them,
you burned them up,
eight of my men died.
Now, you knew
those men. Huh?
They kept you safe,
kept you fed.
As long as I looked
the other way.
Yeah.
Well, it can't be
like that anymore.
Time for you to graduate.
Hey.
I'm gonna tell you
the secret.
There's a threat,
you end it.
And you don't feel ashamed
about enjoying it.
You smell the gunpowder
and you see the blood--
you know what that means?
It means you're alive.
You've won.
You take the heads
so that you don't ever forget.
You kill or you die.
What would
your daughter think
about what you are?
She'd be afraid of me.
But if I had been
like this from the start,
she'd be alive today.
Did you kill Andrea?
( Andrea gasping )
Milton.
Governor:
See? She's still alive.
I'm gonna need her
for something.
Andrea: I heard you
in the other room.
You don't have to lose
any more of your men.
Just stop this.
Your friends
at the prison--
I'm gonna kill them all.
People are gonna help me.
I had to stretch the truth
a little bit, but just a little.
Now they're foaming
at the mouth.
You, get those tools.
I'm not gonna
need them anymore.
Go on.
Careful.
Pick that up.
Come on! Step to.
Let's go.
Hold up.
I'll take that.
Put 'em down.
( Panting )
You're gonna
kill her now.
You're gonna show me
that you've learned something.
Milton...
there is no way
you are leaving this room
without doing it.
So don't make it hard.
Just--
just do it.
That's it.
' ( Grunts)
' ( gasps)
( groans )
( piercing )
( gasping )
I told you
you were gonna do it.
And now you're gonna die.
And you're gonna turn.
And you're gonna tear
the flesh from her bones.
In this life now,
you kill or you die.
Or you die and you kill.
( Theme music playing )
© anoXmous
@ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud
Carl.
I've never seen him
this mad.
Even with Lori.
He just shut down.
He's still a kid.
It's easy to forget.
You know, Merle never did
nothing like that his whole life.
He gave us a chance.
We're ready.
The deal the Governor
offered about me--
you had to think
about it.
You had to.
I get it.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I came real close.
But you didn't.
I never thanked you.
For what?
For getting me
out there that day,
taking me in.
Well, if you didn't have
that baby formula,
I wouldn't have.
You could have
just taken the formula.
Well...
must have been
something else, then.
You know, it was Carl
who made the call.
He said you belonged here.
You're one of us.
Remember, they killed
eight men back there.
- ( Guns clicking)
- Five here last time.
They're no different
from the biters.
They're not gonna stop
until they kill us all,
taken everything
we've worked so hard for.
We're gonna end this
once and for all.
Governor.
This ain't easy to say.
You're gonna have
to count us out.
Sasha:
This isn't our fight.
Tyreese: We'll fight
against the biters,
not other people.
Now we'll stay here
and defend the children.
When you return,
if you want us gone,
no hard feelings.
Thank you.
( Engines start )
Let's roll!
( Snarling )
( pops )
Go!
Governor:
Go, go! Move!
Martinez: Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
( Can clanking )
Give me a flashlight.
Let's split up.
You take a group that way.
You, bring a group,
follow me.
( Door creaking )
Go.
- Andrea: Milton?
- When the tools dropped,
I-I left some pliers
on the floor behind you.
If you can drag--
( pants )
if you can drag your right foot back,
you-- you can get them.
That-- that's it.
- Oh, God.
- Almost.
I'm gonna get us both
out of here.
And you're gonna be okay.
Now when--
when you get free,
you are going to find
something very sharp...
and you are going
to stab me in the head.
That is what
you are going to do.
Keep trying-
Come on.
( Door squeaks )
Hey.
Over there.
- ( Distant clang )
- What was that?
- ( Clatters )
- Shh.
( Distant clatter )
This way.
We took out a few biters
on the south wall.
Other than that,
everything's quiet.
I'll get the next one.
What do you think happens
when they return?
We might have to slip out.
Andrea made it out.
If she's at the prison,
it didn't do her any good.
I'll be right back.
- It's my turn.
- Stay put.
I got it.
( Door closes )
I got it. I got it.
Milton?
( Groans, gasps )
( sighs )
Milton.
Why did you stay...
after you found out
your friends were out there?
I wanted to save everyone.
Even the Governor
for a while.
I had a chance to kill him.
What stopped you?
You know,
this was before.
He was asleep.
I had a knife.
But I tried to stop it all
another way...
because I didn't want
anyone to die.
I'm still here.
I'm still alive.
Yeah.
You are.
You need to hurry.
Right.
Okay.
- ( Explosion )
- ( all shouting )
( alarm blaring )
- Hold your ground!
- ( shouting continues )
Hold your ground!
( Snarling )
(gunfire)
( people screaming )
Get the hell out of here!
( Distant gunfire )
I should be there.
Go.
- ( Coughing )
- ( gunfire)
- Move!
- Go. Go, go, go.
Go.
Move! Move!
Hit it, hit it, hit it!
- Allen: It's not working.
- Go, man!
Shit.
It's jammed!
- Return--
- ( gunfire )
Hey!
They're not going anywhere.
Come on.
( Bullets ricocheting )
We did it?
We did it.
Come on down.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't shoot.
Drop the weapon, son.
Sure.
Here, take it.
-(gunshot)
-(thuds)
( all panting )
We did it.
We drove them out.
We should go after them.
- We should finish it.
- Maggie: It is finished.
Didn't you see them
hightail it out of here?
- Michonne: They could regroup.
- We can't take the chance.
- He's not gonna stop.
- They're right.
We can't keep
living like this.
So we take the fight
back to Woodbury.
We barely made it back
last time.
He don't care.
Yeah.
Let's check on the others.
( Door closes )
( Judith coos )
Hey.
- Hey.
- Dad, I'm coming to Woodbury.
- Carl.
- Dad, I did do my job out there.
Just like all of you.
Took out one
of the Governor's soldiers.
Hershel:
One of his soldiers?
A kid running away?
He stumbled across us.
No, he drew on us.
I'm sorry you had
to do that.
It's what I was there for.
I'm going with you.
( Door opens )
That kid was scared.
He was handing
his gun over.
He said he drew.
Carl said it was
in defense.
I was there.
He didn't have to shoot.
He had every reason
not to--
Maybe it looked like
that to you, Hershel--
Rick!
I'm telling you
he gunned that kid down.
- ( Tires squeal )
-( honking horn )
Move over!
Hey!
I want this truck over.
Go.
Pull in front of them.
( Tires squeal )
What the hell
are you doing?
- We need to dig in.
- Paul: It's not worth it.
- That was a slaughter.
- You bunch of pussies.
I told you we should have
handled this shit ourselves.
We're done fighting
for a hole with a half dozen
psychopaths living in it.
They can keep it.
Allen: You've seen what
they've done-- attacked us.
They killed my boy.
We're going back.
We are not soldiers.
Want us to kill biters, of course.
- But this is crazy.
- Allen: Go home, then.
You think you're
gonna be safe?
Paul: I'm going back
to Woodbury.
We're not here
to settle a grudge.
( Screaming )
(gunfire)
( bird cawing )
( gasping quietly )
(gunshot)
( bird cawing )
( exhales )
( taps )
( pliers scraping )
Come on.
Okay.
All right.
You're still here.
You're still alive.
All right.
Shit!
- All right. Okay.
- ( soft clang )
Michonne.
Hershel told me
about the boy you shot.
He had a gun.
Hmm.
Was he handing it over?
- He had just attacked us.
- Yeah.
Yes, he had.
Was he handing it over?
I couldn't take the chance.
I didn't kill the walker
that killed Dale.
- Look what happened.
- Son, that is not the same thing.
You didn't kill Andrew
and he came back
and killed Mom.
You were in a room
with the Governor
and you let him go.
And then he killed Merle.
I did what I had to do.
Now go.
So he doesn't kill
any more of us.
( Metal clinks)
Rick, we're staying.
We don't know
where the Governor is.
If he comes back,
we'll hold him off.
Just the three of us?
All right.
I appreciate you staying.
Sure.
Come on, come on.
( Crunching )
( snarling )
( bangs )
( hammer clicks )
( snarling )
Come on.
Okay, Okay-
Oh! Come on!
( Andrea screaming )
( Milton snarling )
(thudding )
( metal squeaking )
(gunshot)
Karen:
Tyreese!
- It's me! Don't--
- Get down!
Tyreese:
Karen!
Karen, are you okay?
- I'm fine!
- Where's the Governor?
He fired on everyone.
He killed them all.
- Tyreese: Why are you with them?
- They saved me.
We're coming out!
No.
We're coming out.
Tyreese:
What are you doing here?
We were coming
to finish this
until we saw
what the Governor did.
Tyreese:
He-- he killed them?
Yeah.
Karen told us
Andrea hopped the wall
going for the prison.
She never made it.
She might be here.
Rick: This is where he had
Glenn and Maggie.
Tyreese: The Governor
held people here?
Daryl: He did more
than hold them.
Will you open it?
One, two...
Andrea!
I tried to stop them.
You're burning up.
Judith, Carl,
the rest of them...
Us.
The rest of us.
Are they alive?
Yeah, they're alive.
It's good you found them.
No one can
make it alone now.
They never could.
I just didn't want
anyone to die.
- I can do it myself.
- No.
I have to.
While I still can.
Please?
I know how
the safety works.
Well, I'm not
going anywhere.
I tried.
Yeah.
You did.
(gunshot)
No, it's okay.
What is this?
They're gonna join us.
© anoXmous
@ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud